Laughter and tears. Tragedy and triumph. They lived it all. For the boys.
For the Boys is a drama, music, comedy film directed by Mark Rydell.
Talented USO entertainer Dixie Leonard and comedian Eddie Sparks deal with their relationship over the
course of 5 decades from World War II to the Vietnam War era to their twilight era in the 90's.
Dixie Leonard, played by Bette Midler.
Eddie Sparks, played by James Caan.
Art Silver, played by George Segal.
Shephard, played by Patrick O'Neal.
Danny Leonard, played by Christopher Rydell.
Jeff Brooks, played by Arye Gross.
The Boys (aka The Guys) is a drama/black comedy television
film starring James Woods and John Lithgow.
It was directed by Glenn Jordan, who had previously worked with Woods on the 1986 TV movie
Promise and later worked with Woods again in 1994 for the TV drama film Jane's House.
The film first aired on September 15, 1991 on the ABC Network.
The film explores themes of concert, dancer, entertainer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.